<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on Amazon Pinpoint Workshop</title>
    <link>https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on Amazon Pinpoint Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What We&#39;ll Build</title>
      <link>https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/10_what_we_will_build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/10_what_we_will_build/</guid>
      <description>Our Goal In this workshop, we&amp;rsquo;ll build an app with features including:
   The Architecture Here&amp;rsquo;s a map of the services we&amp;rsquo;ll use and how they&amp;rsquo;ll all connect.
Our Tools If we were to try and build scalable and highly-available systems to handle each of the above concerns on our own, we&amp;rsquo;d probably never get around to building our app! Fortunately, AWS provides services and tooling to handle a lot of the undifferentiated heavy lifting involved in building modern, robust applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinpoint Setup</title>
      <link>https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/20_pinpoint_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/20_pinpoint_setup/</guid>
      <description>to do: fix region in urls sandbox info should we educate on endpoint limits Test SMS image  Step 1: Create Pinpoint Project This workshop has been tested in {{INSERT REGION HERE}}
Initial Configuration  First head to Amazon Pinpoint in the AWS Console. Enter a project name of pinpointWorkshop and click on the &amp;lsquo;Create a project&amp;rsquo; button  For this workshop we will cover Email and SMS And voice, so first of all click on Configure underneath Email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinpoint Basics</title>
      <link>https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/30_pinpoint_basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/30_pinpoint_basics/</guid>
      <description>to do: fix region in urls issue with send on timezone. add images fir creating a segment add images for creating a campaign cleanup csv (and ensure it is setup for journeys lab)  Creating a segment What is a segment - insert definition   Click on segments Upload Segment (sample segment.csv replace email and mobile numbers)  Create a Message Template Create a Campaign  create a campagin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Journeys</title>
      <link>https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/40_pinpoint_journeys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pinpoint-workshop.com/20_getting_started/40_pinpoint_journeys/</guid>
      <description>Update onboarding workflow. modify img path to /images&amp;rdquo; rahter than /images remove symlink dynamic segments - &amp;lsquo;and who have used your app within the past 30 days.&amp;rsquo; also add content. ensure there is a message template section in pinpoint basics upload Message Templates remove journey exit from full diagram check that segments down stream can change once a journey has started inacurate total endpoints journey wait times. flow vs journey consistency [ ]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>